totsy.com 2012-05-04

# Totsy, the private sale site for Moms

Unfortunately, JavaScript is currently disabled or not supported by your browser. Please enable JavaScript for full functionality.

## Totsy's Privacy Policy:

Valid as of August 24, 2011

* * *

The privacy of our Members is important to us. Please read our Privacy Policy below so you understand how Totsy collects information about our Members, what type of information we collect about our Members, why we collect such information, how we protect personal information about our Members and in which limited circumstances TOTSY may have to share such information with other parties.

## 1\. TOTSY's Privacy Policy.

* * *

The information we collect through our Site helps us provide you with information specific to your needs and interests. This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") covers TOTSY's website, www.totsy.com (the "Site"). Please read below to review our Privacy Policy and the types of information we gather through our Site. In this Privacy Policy, "we", "us", "our" and other similar references mean TOTSY and "you" and "your" and other similar references mean a specific user of the Site. By visiting the Site, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

Totsy has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information.  TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at 888-247-9444.  If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site.

## 2\. How TOTSY Gather and Use Information About Its Members?

* * *

## (i) Cookies.

* * *

Cookies are pieces of data assigned by a web server that uniquely identify the browser on your PC. Websites typically use temporary cookies called "session" cookies to ensure that you are recognized when you move from page to page within one site and that any information you have entered is remembered. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. For example, if an e-commerce site did not use session cookies then items placed in a shopping basket would disappear by the time you reach the checkout. Websites also use cookies called "persistent" cookies to enable a website to remember you on subsequent visits, speeding up or enhancing your experience of services or functions offered. TOTSY attempts to install both persistent and session cookies when a user arrives at our Site. Cookies enable our systems to gather information about your navigational patterns through the site. Viewers have the option to accept or disable cookies at any time through their browsers. For more information about how to delete cookies from your web browser, you will usually find responses in the "help" menu of your web browser. Please note that if you block or refuse to accept cookies, or delete cookies between visits to the site, you may not be able to access or use certain features or functions of our Site.

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order for you to use the shopping cart, etc. 

## (ii) Server Statistics.

* * *

We and our third party tracking partners collect general statistics to track user trends on our Site. These statistics include hits to our server, the types of browsers used to access our Site, page views, and navigational patterns. The information that is collected in this manner does NOT provide us with any personally identifiable information about our users. It helps us track "where" our users are coming from. This allows us to pinpoint high traffic areas and determine the most effective ways to communicate with our users. 

As part of that ongoing analysis, TOTSY also uses devices called "web beacons" to help us identify when emails sent to you have been received and read. In order to prevent the introduction of viruses and hackers into the TOTSY site we may collect information, such as IP addresses, into a log file to be used to identify potential hackers of the TOTSY site.

## (iii) Personal Information You Provide To Us.

* * *

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, "Personal Information" is any information that identifies you, would enable someone to contact you, or that describes your relationship with TOTSY. We collect and store Personal Information (such as email address, name, address, phone number) when you register to use our Site, ask a question, complete a form, conduct a transaction, or send us an email. While you are not required to submit any information to our Site, if you do not provide the requested information, you may not be able to access or use some of the features and functions of our Site and we may not be able to provide you with certain services. TOTSY uses your Personal Information to complete transactions, respond to your requests, deliver the products and services you request, and notify you of promotions, updates, or special offers that we think may interest you.

## 3\. Communications From The Site

* * *

**Newsletters**

When you register on our site, we will use your email address to send you our newsletter and emails letting you know about our daily sales. If you wish to no longer receive these emails you may do so by following the unsubscribe instructions contained within each of the communications you receive. 

**Service-related Announcements**

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so.  For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. 

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.  If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

## 4\. Tell-A-Friend

* * *

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Totsy stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

You can import contacts from your Outlook or other email account address book to invite them to become members of our site.  We collect the username and password for the email account you wish to import your contacts from and will only use it for that purpose. 

Your friend may contact us at [support@totsy.com](mailto:support@totsy.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

## 5\. What Security Procedures Does TOTSY Use To Protect Personal Information of Its Members?

* * *

The privacy of our members is important to us. We use physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to assist us in preventing unauthorized access, maintaining data accuracy, and correctly using your Personal Information. Except as specified in this Privacy Policy, we use commercially reasonable efforts to limit access to your Personal Information to the employees, agents, and officers of TOTSY who need the information for the performance of their jobs.

## 6\. Will TOTSY Disclose The Information It Collects To Outside Parties?

* * *

TOTSY warrants that its employees, agents, officer and directors, consultants or subcontractors are obligated to and will hold any Personal Information in strict confidence and to take all reasonable measures to ensure that confidentiality is respected. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.  We do not sell your personal information to third parties. TOTSY may share information with carefully selected vendors and business partners with whom we work. This includes companies that offer affinity, frequent-user, and reward programs; and, companies that perform marketing services and other business operations for us such as a shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services, an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf, live chat software to assist you if you have questions regarding our service while you are on the site, and third party service provider to allow you to comment on our blog and share some portions of our site with others. All companies that act on our behalf are contractually obligated to keep all information confidential and to use the Member information only to provide the services we ask them to perform for you and us. We may provide aggregate statistics about our Members, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third party vendors, but these statistics do not include Personal Information. We may disclose Personal Information we collect from you if required by law, or in the good-faith belief that disclosure is necessary (a) to obey the law or comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates; (b) to protect and defend our rights or property or the rights or property of other users of our Site; or (c) to act in an emergency to protect the personal safety of users of our Site or the public.

If Totsy is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets,  you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

## 7\. Accessing Your Personally Identifyable Information

* * *

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete/deactivate it by making the change on our member information page [support@totsy.com](mailto:support@totsy.com)

or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## 8\. Security

* * *

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## 9\. External Links. About Other Entities Which May Have Links on Their Sites to Our Site.

* * *

We are not responsible for how non affiliated companies or organizations collect, use, disclose, or secure the information that you provide to them. If you choose to access a third party website linked to our Site, you do so at your own risk and subject to any terms of service or privacy policy (if any) associated with such third party websites.

## 10\. Facebook Connect Or Other OpenID Provider

* * *

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

## 11\. Testimonials

* * *

We provide you with the opportunity to send us video testimonials. While we screen these testimonials for content you should be aware that any information you provide in them may be collected, and used by others who view them. If you want your testimonial removed please contact us at [support@totsy.com](mailto:support@totsy.com).

## 12\. Public Forums

* * *

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [support@totsy.com](mailto:support@totsy.com).  In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## 13\. Collection Of Information From Children.

* * *

TOTSY does not direct any of our content specifically to children nor do we knowingly collect personal information from individuals under the age of 13. If we learn that a user is under thirteen (13) years of age, we will promptly delete any Personal Information we have collected about that user.

## 14\. Consent To Processing In The United States.

* * *

By providing any Personal Information to TOTSY, all users, including, without limitation, users in Canada and the member states of the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to this Privacy Policy and to the transfer of such Personal Information across international borders in accordance with TOTSY's standard operations, including the collection, storage, and processing of such information in the United States of America, and waive any rights that they may have under their local laws which would conflict with TOTSY's Privacy Policy.

## 15\. Your California Privacy Rights.

* * *

As provided by California Civil Code Section 1798.83, a California resident who has provided Personal Information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes ("California Member") is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed Personal Information to any third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of Personal Information, upon receipt of a request by a California Member, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom Personal Information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of Personal Information that were disclosed.

However, under the law, a business is not required to provide the above-described lists if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its privacy policy) a policy of not disclosing Member's Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the Member first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, as long as the business maintains and discloses this policy. Rather, the business may comply with the law by notifying the California Member of his or her right to prevent disclosure of Personal Information and providing a cost free means to exercise that right.

As stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure -- typically by opting in to receive information from a third party that is participating in some activity describes on our site. If you do ask us to share your information with a third party for its marketing purposes, we will only share information in connection with that specific activity, as we do not share information with any third party on a continual basis. To prevent disclosure of your Personal Information for use in direct marketing by a third party, do not opt in to such use when you provide Personal Information on our site. Please note that whenever you opt in to receive future communications from a third party, your information will be subject to the third party's privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use information. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.

California Member may request further information about our compliance with this law by contacting us on our website under the CONTACT US menu. Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per Member each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through our Site.

## 16\. Modification And Notification Of Changes.

* * *

TOTSY may at its sole discretion edit this Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) and/or by means of a prominent notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

## 17\. In Summary.

* * *

TOTSY is committed to protecting your privacy. The information collected from our Site helps us better understand our market and consumer interests. This allows us to serve our Members and business associates with the level of satisfaction they deserve.

If you have questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices please contact us via email at [support@totsy.com](mailto:support@totsy.com) or via postal mail at 10 West 18th street 4th Floor New York, NY 10011, Thank you.
